I'm the programmer in the world.
I'm not gonna be guilty.
I'm gonna be relaxed.
I'm gonna be like, I don't want to die.
Okay, alright.
I'm not gonna be a survivor.
Get away from, I don't wanna die.
Let's go.
There you go!
One, two, three Come and find a way!
I find a way
Break out
Here is my one and only
trusted assistant, Charlotte.
Hello.
Charlotte, dear,
if you would please give our prisoners a
brief rundown of what
their lives will be like?
for the foreseeable future.
Sure.
Here in this prison facility, we
represent the ideas of our country!
placing emphasis on equality.
If you wish to wander around
or partake in exercise,
you are free to do so
in a designated area.
You can use the phones, take
a shower, or read books.
An exemplary prisoner can
even have a TV in their cell.
Some may be allowed to work and are given
a chance to study for a college degree.
You heard her, and that's not all.
Ah, yes, Charlotte, do
you have a question?
I just remembered, there are rules that
must be followed too, aren't there?
Why, of course, Charlotte,
you're absolutely right.
First,
under no circumstances are
you allowed to take off
the wristband with your
designated prisoner number.
Second, there will be no borrowing
or lending things among inmates,
and any metal materials are prohibited.
Is wearing earring still okay?
Shut your mouth right this instant!
The chief is speaking!
No, they're not allowed,
inmate FE40536 Joling Code.
If you have any further inquiries, please
ask the guards and they can assist you.
Orientation is complete! All right!
Everyone, turn and face to your left!
This place is huge.
I hear the prison covers
this whole island.
Oh, alligator.
F .E.
40536, welcome to your
new home, cell number 206.
Break time for today is come and gone.
The cell opens at 6.30 a .m.
Breakfast begins at 7 a .m., but if
you wish to sleep in, you're allowed.
Hope you two can get along.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
The name's Jolene.
My name is Gwess. Want some?
Thank you.
But so much stuff happened today
that I just don't have an appetite.
What's your problem?
I know you're new here, but
the bottom book is mine!
Are you gonna have a problem with
that, you stupid little whore?!
Bee!
Jojo! Bee!
Look, I'm not interested in fighting you.
I saw your stuff on the top
bed, so I thought it was yours.
Why is that here?!
What is wrong with you?!
Now you're trying to jack my stuff too?!
No!
I just want to see that closer!
Please listen to me!
If you open that charm,
you'll find a small stone and
a picture of my parents inside.
It may be the one I threw away
Is that so?
I bought this for two bucks
from a new inmate the other day.
It's pretty, wouldn't you say?
Yeah, sure.
Just let me see.
Get your hands off me, you filthy bitch.
No way.
I'm letting you see it
Fine, I'll buy it off of you. Go ahead.
Name your price
200 bucks. What the hell?
Didn't you hear me dumbass? I said 200
Bitch
Let's out!
The heck's up with everything?
So many strange things happened.
My mind is racing with thoughts.
I hate this.
I feel so lonely, I could cry.
What are you doing?!
About last night.
I'm really sorry. Huh?
Morning?
Take it.
Huh?
Don't worry, it's fine if you look.
Although, that pic of your
parents wasn't in there.
Sorry, but I don't think this
is the charm you're looking for.
See?
Was anything inside at all? Like a stone?
Sorry, there wasn't.
Anyway, can you forgive
my actions from yesterday?
You see, I'm a coward.
Especially when meeting new people.
It's okay.
If anything, it was my fault for assuming.
I'm still learning how things work here.
Wow, Jolene, you're such a nice person.
I hope we can become close friends.
Yeah, I'd like that too.
Oh, there's the buzzer.
Looks like it's breakfast time.
See you there, bestie.
Hey, wait for me!
I'm coming with you!
Are you serious?
What's up with all this water?
My pants are soaking wet now!
What am I gonna do?
Excuse me, but what do you mean
the food's sold out already?
I haven't even had my meal yet!
Can't you see it's gone?
Here at GD, you've got
the freedom to sleep in,
just like you have the
freedom to arrive late.
Shouldn't you have food
prepared for everyone?
You've got to at least have a banana left!
That's what we call one of
the Seven Wonders of Prison.
What does that mean?
Oh, Jolyne, guess you decided to sleep in.
I'm so full, I couldn't eat another bite.
Glass, hold on!
Did I just see two milks and
two bananas on your tray?
No way.
Why would I have two?
That'd be selfish.
Oh, by the way, sorry about all
the water I spilled on the floor.
Don't worry, I'll clean it all up later.
I already took care of it.
Wow, that's so nice of you.
Thanks a bunch, Jolyne.
Wait, this is...
This is your chance.
Fly over here and take a look.
I believe you can do it with all my heart.
You can do anything
with the power of love.
Yes, as long as we trust each
other, anything is possible.
Now give it a try.
You're so freaking adorable.
I knew you could pull it off for me.
Coffee chop!
That was great!
Here, have a treat, darling!
Good morning!
Now, we've talked about this.
You don't greet me with good morning.
It's love you, remember?
Now, let's try again.
It's much cuter when you
say you love me, you know?
I love you!
Yes!
Good, good, good, good, good!
That's my perfect little man, coffee chop!
Now, something harder.
Try flying to my finger.
To build trust between us, we have to
take risks here and there, Kapi-Chan.
What's wrong with you?
Just get on with it!
What? Whoa?
What did you just say?
Do little birdies say,
whoa, where you come from?
Hey, now, don't you start messing with me.
Do you got some superficial idea
about what love and trust should be?
Huh? Do you?
Well, you've broken that trust.
I'm done with you.
Did something just go by?
A banana?
What is up with this weird bird?
No way.
Small, but it has to be real.
There's a tiny person
inside, and she killed them!
Glass. That woman.
The only explanation for this is
she has that stone from the amulet,
and it gave her some
kind of special ability.
But what the hell is
with that small human?
Wha...
What is going on now?
What the hell?
My body...
Did it just shrink?
So the culprit was you.
How did you take my
copychan away from me?!
Jolene! Jolene! Jolene! Jolene!
Jolene, I'm starting to
like you more and more.
I knew we'd be good friends.
What's going on with my body?
What did you do?
Hey, Jolene, listen.
I need you to stop talking, okay?
I'm like that person in the parrot!
I said stop talking!
Put this on!
I already removed all the guts.
The parrot had some disadvantages.
The poor thing couldn't
hold or carry things.
But rats are better.
They've got four paws.
As for him, he was a guard
who got fired for being lazy.
The chief and everyone
thinks he already went home.
And by the way, I know
I told you not to speak,
but I'll let it slide if
you do it in a cutesy way.
Mike, see you later.
Oh, Mommy, I'm hungry.
Please feed me.
Yeah, okay?
Look at you, so stinking adorable.
Now, let's begin your training.
Faster, faster, faster, faster!
Show me some hustle!
Now lift them up, Chorokichi.
Chorokichi?
Everything has a name, you know.
In the beginning was the Word,
and the Word was with God.
And the Word was God, and
through Him all was made.
And without Him nothing was
made that had been made.
So this mental power that
shrank you deserves a name.
How about Jojo Dolls?
Yes, that will be the
name of my mental ability.
Let's add another book.
Naughty girl.
Are you being cunning and trying to cheat?
Hey now, you're not gonna
betray my trust, are you?
You're not trying to ruin
our relationship, are you?
I'm just messing with you.
Congrats, Todokichi, you passed.
You're going to need that
cunning wit for your next task.
Very, very good!
Can you see?
At the far end of this corridor,
you're going to find a control center.
Your objective is to get
to that switch over there.
It can unlock all the cells
and doors in this prison.
I know you can make it.
You understand what I'm saying?
If we work together, we can escape.
For some reason, I can't
make myself smaller.
Though luckily, we have you now.
But it's important we trust each other.
Of course, the actual
commencement is further ahead.
For this mission, you just need to
investigate everything beyond this corridor.
Do you really think we
can escape like this?
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't go forgetting I told you
to speak in a cutesy way now!
This control center?
How exactly am I supposed
to crawl over to it?
You're such a Code!
That's my adorable baby rat girl!
But don't ask me, you dumbass.
Figuring that part out is your job.
Look above you.
There's a surveillance camera.
You'll be in its blind spot
if you go under the handrail.
So just go straight below it
and keep the rat corpse on.
Okay, hurry up and go!
Hey!
What are you doing over there?
Girl with the headband!
Who are you?
Tell me your name and prison number!
The number's FE18081, and my name is Wes.
I'm just taking a walk around
the corridors if you don't
have any business here get
away from the gate and leave
Sure, mr.
Guard
There are four steel doors in here.
I wonder which one of
them leads to the control
center and there are cameras
in the corner two of them?
What the why is it so tight! I...
suddenly...
Huh?
What the hell was that sound just now?
Yeah, man, I heard that too.
It's close.
Oh crap, that's not good.
My body's getting bigger!
It was just a coffee maker.
Ain't that the sound it
makes when it's ready?
Uh-uh.
That sounds like something else.
Why is this happening now?
Distance.
Is it because Quest left?
Is distance related to her ability?
I definitely heard it!
It's gotta be in here somewhere!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
It's coming from there!
Hey, get out of the way! Move it!
Ah!
That's freaking hard!
Damn it, YB!
Huh?
I told you idiots it was the coffee
maker, but you wouldn't listen!
My bad.
Screw this investigation!
I have to fit through the bars
before my body grows any bigger!
What the hell?!
Gee. Gee. Dolph.
This thing is...
Jojo!
So creepy.
It seems like a doll,
but it's transparent.
Same as my thread.
It's a physical manifestation of
Gwess' energy that no one else can see!
How about Jojo dolls?
Yes, that will be the
name of my mental ability.
This baby doll from hell is what shrunk me
and ripped the guard and
the parrot to pieces!
That must mean it was just chilling
inside the rat with me the entire time!
And I'm willing to bet that Gwess has no
idea her ability weakens if she's far away,
so she doesn't know my
body's growing back!
Now I've got a murderous
munchkin chasing me
down because it thinks
that I was running away!
If I don't get out of here,
the thing's gonna kill me!
G. Damn it. G.
Dolls.
What did I ever do to
deserve a fate like this?
This is how I go out?
By this creature?
I can't get through!
G. G.
G.
A thread.
No, a whole clump of threads.
This must be the form that
my energy takes. A clump.
When they gather and clump,
it becomes three-dimensional.
What a concept!
Scream your heart out, bastard child!
Now call Gwess over here and hurry up!
Jolene, I wasn't expecting
you to also have an ability.
Come here!
Wait a second, please,
Jolene, I'm begging you!
Stop strangling my GG doll so tightly!
Hey, I don't want to hear it!
Focus on shrinking my body enough
so I can squeeze out of here,
but only just a little, got it?
Okay, okay, you can even
have the bottom bunk, too.
I know we've been through a
lot, but please don't hate me.
Still, though, I'd like you to speak
to me all cutesy from time to time.
Just hurry and do it already!
Uh, alright.
Now hand over the amulet.
That includes the stone inside, and I
want to know who you bought it from, too.
Of course, whatever you say.
That'll be $200.
Shut the fuck up, you bitch!
Just tell me the name before I kill you!
Okay, I got it.
Well, uh, I'm not sure, but I
think her name was Hermes. Hermes?
I don't know her that well.
Here.
Kidding.
Gotcha!
Oh, Mr. Guard!
Hurry, come here!
There's a prisoner past the gunpoint!
Hurry up and get over here!
Hey you, the hell are you doing in there?
How'd you get past the door?
Prison break! Code 999!
This is gonna be the end of you!
If you didn't know,
that guard just went to pick up his
shotgun and since you're behind the door,
he's got the right to shoot your ass!
No questions asked!
Jolene!
I'd say it's just what you deserve!
You hurt my feelings, and
now you're gonna die for it!
Good freakin' grief, Quest. Shut up!
And listen, you said everything
has a name, didn't you?
Then I'll name my ability, too.
It'll be Stone Ocean, cause somehow I'm
gonna free myself from the Sea of Stone.
Did you hear me?
Stone Ocean, that's the name.
Hold on!
If there's some sort of
hierarchy in this prison,
then I'll follow it as much as I need to.
But I'm the one who's gonna
be giving out orders here.
Now shrink me down and get me
the hell out of this hallway!
Huh?
Hold on, where did she go?
She's gone!
Are you really sure you saw her?
Well, yeah, but I only
saw her from the back.
Weird.
Old man.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do?
In my life,
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming far
away from today.
Thank you.